Guide to the Administrative Files of the Dean of the School of Education, Daniel E. Griffiths 1948-1985 (Bulk 1965-1983) RG 26.0.1 RG.26.0.1
New York University Archives
- Griffiths Container List
  - NYU - Commission on Coordinate Liberal Arts Studies, 1970-1973 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Committee Curriculum, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Organization, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Committee for Urban Affairs, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Day Care Project - Balter, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Advisory Secondary Education, undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Degree Requirements, undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Computer Users Group, undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Problems - Students - Cases to be resolved / Cases Solved, undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Dean Ziobrowski's Study of Student Drop-Outs, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Commission on Academic Planning, 1976-1977 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Information Systems Planning Study, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Deans Review of Vice Presidential Areas, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Planning, Commission on, 1974-1976 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Teacher Education, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Borowitz, Sidney - Chancellor (Correspondence), 1971-1977 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Consultants' Reports - Reading File - Self-Evaluation, undated (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Deafness Rehabilitation - Naiman / Vernon, undated (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Educational Theatre - Swartzell / Roberts, undated (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - English Ed. - Vine / Hook, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 195 4
  - Media Ecology - Oran / Garden, undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Speech Communication - Fluharty / DeVito, undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Speech Pathology & Audiology - Martin / Morris, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - TESOL - Nadler / Knapp, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Counselor Education and Counseling Psychology - Hamburger / Gladstein and Esposito/Dole, undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Philosophy of Education and History of Education - Mattingly/Raywid and Mattingly/Church, undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Religious Education - Thompson / Miller, undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Hebrew Culture and Education - Winter / Orlinsky, undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Bilingual Education - Sanchez / Brisk, undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Business Education - Sapre / Anderson, undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Communications in Education - Ruderman / Wagner, undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Social Studies - Hosay / Metcalf, undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Early Childhood & Elementary Ed. - Ely / Haberman, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Languages Program Evaluation, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Access Restrictions
    No Subnote Content
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 233 3
  - Evaluation of Doctoral Program in International Education, 1971-1978 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    There are restrictions to Program Evalution in regards to student transcripts and faculty CV's
  - Physical Education and Sport Program Evaluation Bucher / Eyler, 1967-1977 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Physical Education and Sports Evaluation for "Phase Out", 1979 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    Access Restrictions to CV's of professors with social security numbers and student transcripts with grades.
  - Doctoral Program of Physical Education Individual Faculty Reports, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - GSAS - Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - GSAS correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Bobst Library Dean Eugene Kennedy, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Capital Campaign Program, Grants, Funds, Foundations, Alumni, 1963-1968 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Capital Campaign Program, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - School of Continuing Education Dean Russell F. W. Smith, 1965-1975 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Development Program: Noreen T. Shipman, 1974-1976 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Science Ed, 1970-1976 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Secondary Ed, 1971-1975 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Languages, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - International Ed, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Physical Ed and Sport - Bucher / Eyler, undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Physical Ed and Sport II - Bucher / Alley, undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Bobst Library - Dean Eugene Kennedy, undated (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Money Capital Program, Grants, Funds, Found, Alumni, 1963-1968 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Capital Campaign Program, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - NYU School of Continuing Ed, 1965-1975 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Development Program, 1974-1976 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Division of Nursing, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Center for Ed Research and Field Services, 1968-1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 234 1
  - Commission on Effective Uses of Resources, 1969-1971 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Hawkinshire, Frank - Confidential File, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Spencer Foundation Seed Grants, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Spencer Foundation - General, 1971-1977 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Spencer Foundation Grants Commission, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Controller / Treasurer, Mr. J. Whiteside, 1969-1975 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Undergrad Education, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - University Without Halls, 1970-1974 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Doctoral Council Meeting, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Doctoral Council, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Doctoral Council, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 235 8
  - Dr. Daniel Griffin, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Richard Lousdale, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Doctoral Council, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence III, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence II, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence I, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Guidelines NYS Review, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Clusters, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Consultants NYS Doctoral Review, undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - NYS Deans, undated (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Travel Vouchers - Doctoral Council, undated (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Site Visits, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Characteristics of the Ph.D. Thesis, undated (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Deans Group / Division Heads, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 236 6
  - Summary of Recommendations Resulting from Doctoral Review, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Expenses: Self Evaluation, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Self Study - Correspondence with Consultants, undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Self Study - List of Consultants, undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Self Study - Schedules for Consultants' Visits, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Psychological Foundations of Reading, undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Research Design, Measurement, and Evaluation, undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Special Education, undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - School Psychology, undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - House Economics and Nutrition, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - General Educational Psychology, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Leisure Studies, undated (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Mathematics Education, undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Science Education, undated (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Educational Administration, undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 237 4
  - Educational Psychology, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Higher Education, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Safety Sciences and Education, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Rehabilitation Counseling, undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Nursing, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Health Education / Commmunity - Hamburg / Sinacore, undated (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Occupational Therapy, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Human Sexuality, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Dance Education - Rowe / Hawkins, undated (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Music Education, undated (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Technology and Industrial Education, undated (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Creative Arts, undated (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Doctoral Programs: Self Evaluation, undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 238 2
  - Bilingual Education - Brisk, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Business Education - Anderson, undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Communications in Education - Wagner, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Counselor Education - Glaidstein, undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Counseling Psychology - Dole, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Deafness Rehabilitation - Vernon, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Early Childhood & Elementary Ed. - Haberman, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Educational Administration - Hoy, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Educational Sociology - Corwin, undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Educational Theatre - Roberts, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - English Ed - Hook, undated (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Languages - Allen, undated (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Gen. Ed. Psychology - Mathis, undated (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Hebrew Culture and Education - Orlinsky, undated (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Higher Education, undated (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - History of Education - Church, undated (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Home Economics and Nutrition - Brancher, undated (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - International Education - Remy, undated (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Guidelines - Leisure Studies, undated (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - 2nd Self Evaluation, undated (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Leisure Studies - Mundy, undated (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Mathematics Ed - Nichols, undated (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Media Ecology - Garden, undated (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Philosophy of Ed - Rayund, undated (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Physical Education and Sport - Eyler, undated (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Appeals: Physical Education and Sport, undated (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Psychological Foundations of Reading, undated (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Religious Education - Miller, undated (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Research Design and Management, undated (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Appeals: Science Education, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 239 0
  - Science Education, 1976-1982 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Science Education: Klopfer, 1978-1982 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - School Psychology: Hyman, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Secondary Education: Mikekon, 1978-1982 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Appeals: Secondary Education, undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Appeals: Secondary Education, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Social Studies Education: Metcalf, 1978-1982 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Special Education: MacMillian, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Speech Communication: DeVito, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Speech Pathology and Audiology: Morris, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - TESOL: Knapp, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Division of Health: Doctoral Programs Self Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Human Sexuality: Kirkendra, 1978-1983 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Community Health Education: Sinacare, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Health Education in Schools and Colleges: Sinacare, 1981-1982 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Occupational Therapy: Schebly, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Physical Therapy: Rose, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Rehabilitation Counseling: Sinick, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Safety Sciences and Education - Mills, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Division of Nursing: Doctoral Programs - Self-Evaluation, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Research and Theory Development in Nursing, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Division of Arts and Arts Education, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Art and Art Education - Eisner, 1982-1983 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Dance and Dance Education - Irning, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Music and Music Education, 1978-1983 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Technology and Industrial Education: 2nd Self Evaluation, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Technology and Industrial Education, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Creative Arts, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Public Hearing on NY State Plan, 1972-1973 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Elmira Hearing on Teacher Certification, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Certification, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Administrative Performance Certification Program, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - Recertification of Programs of Early Childhood and Elementary Education, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - Recertification of Programs for Speech and Hearing Handicapped, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - Recertification of Teachers of Special Ed in NYS, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 240 8
  - Certification Program, undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - School of Ed Faculty: Art Education, undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - School of Ed Bilingual Dept. Correspondence, 1970-1977 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - School of Ed Faculty Educational Administration, 1970-1975 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Educational Psychology, undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Educational Statistics, 1971-1974 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - School of Education Faculty: English, Speech, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Mathematics and Science, Division of Stephen Willoughby, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - School of Ed Faculty: Music Education, undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - School of Ed: Physical Therapy, undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Science Education, 1970-1976 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Secondary Ed.: Profs. Miller and Robertson, 1971-1975 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 241 6
  - Professor Louse Hock, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Organization of the School of Education, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Admissions, 1963-1968 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Admissions: Undergrad Statistics, 1974-1977 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Belgian Principals' Visit, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Budget - Weekly Status Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Budget - Weekly Status Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - College for a Day - English Education, Prof. Marilyn Sobelman, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Doctoral Fees, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Doctoral Research Design Guidelines, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Education Project, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Evaluation of Faculty, Committee, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Compensation, 1961-1965 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Handbook, NYU, School of Education, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Salary and Promotion (Female), 1971 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Record Examination, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Harlem Institute for Teachers, 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - International Studies, Center for, 1967-1974 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Labor Relations Advisory Council, 1970-1973 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Learning to Learn Project, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Librarian: Education, Barbara Marks, 1967-1974 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Library: Education, 1969-1974 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Management Forum, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Masters Degree in Journalism: Proposal / Report, 1966-1967 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Masters Degree Programs in Spain, 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - New School Seal, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Office Services, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Physical Therapy Accreditation Report, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Printing and Publishing Committee, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Puerto Rico Bilingual, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Puerto Rico Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Puerto Rico: College of the Sacred Heart, 1971-1975 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 242 4
  - Radio / TV Activity, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Registration Reports: Office of the Registrar, 1963-1975 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Registration: Summer Sessions Dean Blustain, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Student Activities and Services: Committee Report, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Student Evaluations of Faculty (Course Evaluations), 1974 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Student Teaching Strike, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Student Strike, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Standardization Practices and Requirements for Deposits, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Study Abroad, 1972-1975 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Summer Sessions, Dean Jonah Blustain, 1972-1975 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1975-1977 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Teacher Education, NYU Commission on, 1969-1972 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Open Hearings on the Future of the School, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Future of the School - Commission on the Mission of the School, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - President's Council of the School of Education, 1971-1973 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Advisory Committee on Planning for the Future of the School, 1972-1974 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Future of the School - Position of the Division Head, undated (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Future of the School - Research Material, undated (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Future of the School of Education - Drafts of Final Document, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 243 2
  - Future of the School of Education - Working Drafts, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - All Square Student Congress, 1967-1969 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Ed Alumni Board of Directors, 1966-1974 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Proposal, National Center for Archives of American Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - NYC Board of Examiners, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Brazil Project, 1970-1972 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Eleazor Bromberg Deputy Chancellor, 1971-1975 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Joseph A. Byrnes Ass. Sec. For University, 1970-1975 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Commencement, 1975-1979 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Congressmen, Letters to, undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Deafness Research and Training Center, Education and Training Comm., 1970-1974 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - DRAT Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - DRAT Advisory Board, 1972-1975 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Federal Regulations "Family Educational Rights and Privacy" Act, undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Futurism, 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Grade Inflation, Article, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Hebrew Culture and Education - Winter, Director, 1970-1975 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Jan Plan, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Jas. Kirby, General Council, 1971-1975 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 244 0
  - Mr. Morton Myers Deputy Chancellor of Admin. Services, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - NCPEA, 1969-1970 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Senate Meetings, 1970-1974 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Senate Calendar Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Senatorial Election, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Senate Committee Organization and Governance, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Senate Committee Powers of the Senate, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Senate Committee Ad Hoc Comm. Student Evaluation of Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Senate Committee Student Records, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Student Senate, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Senate Educational Policies Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 245 7
  - Senate Purposes and Guidelines, 1970-1971 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Senate Purposes and Guidelines: Regarding Sampus Tension / Strike, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Senate, Student Evaluation of Undergraduate Courses, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Apex Report, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Apex Project - Professor Virgil Clift, undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Research Applications - Research Support, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Research - Assignment, Review - Reporting, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Research - Center for Economic Education, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Research - Barnard - COPES, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Research - Fringe Benefits Expense, undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Research - R&D Center Guidance, undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Research - Institute for Computer Research in the Humanities, undated (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Development Studies (IDS), 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Institute for Development Studies, 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Kurland (Meeting arranged by JA), 1967 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Miller Proposal to Stern Family - meeting with David Hunter, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Staff Relations - Prof. Evans, undated (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - NDEA Coordinators' meeting, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Rederfer Proposals, undated (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - R:Disc Materials Research Center, undated (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Policy Center Proposal, undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 246 5
  - Office of Educational Research Services, undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Research Reports (Summaries), undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Research Services, undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Projects-Sexton: Proposal undert Title #1 of Higher Ed. Act of 1965, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Grants or Funded Projects, undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Projects-Griffiths:TOBE - Extra Copies of Proposal, undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Tri-University Project, 1968-1971 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Responses Received to our "test" mailing, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Costs Applicable to Research and Development - Office of Education, undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Research-USOE: Field Reader Policy, undated (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Research-USOE: Instructions for Preparing Reports, undated (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Projects: R.Weiss: Center for Research in Exercise, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Research: R.Weiss: Proposed Executive Training, undated (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - IDS/DEG Jamaica Project, undated (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Title IV - Supervisors and Curriculum Leaders on Problems of Desegregation, undated (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - NDEA Counseling and Guidance Training Institute, undated (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - NDEA Institute for Teachers of Disadvantage Youth (Clift), undated (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - NDEA English Institute (Walter Gibson), undated (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Propsal: "The Preparation of Adminstrators from Central America", undated (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Report of Placement Services, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, To-For and From President James Hester, undated (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Presidential Search - President John C.Sawhill selected, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report (Manuscript), 1970 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 247 3
  - Annual Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report - The Center or Safety, 1970-1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Report of the TTT Project in Science and Mathematics, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Summary of Active Candidates / Positions Listed, 1970-1971 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - British Teacher Center - B. Rosner, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - School of Education Directory, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Sample Letter File, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Xerox Requests, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Telephone Bills, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Financial Emergency Task Force (FETF), 1972 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 248 1
  - FETF: Comments from University Committee, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - FETF: University Committee, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - FETF: University Heights, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - FETF: Student Activities, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - FETF: School of Social Work, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - FETF: Medical Center, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - FETF: Libraries, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - FETF: Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - FETF: Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - FETF: Cost Accounting - School of Education, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - FETF: Computers, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - FETF: Central Services, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - FETF: 3-Year Budget Projections, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - FETF: Financial Reports, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - FETF: School of Education Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - FETF: Free Standing Operations, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - FETF: Final Report, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - FETF: Undergraduate Sub-Committee, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - FETF: Undergraduate Education, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - FETF: References Etc., 1972 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 249 9
  - FETF: Working Documents, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - FETF: Mercer Report, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - FETF: Report to Trustees, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 4)